Did the listing actually say "miniature"?
(Leonard:)I just assumed.
Well, who sells a full-sized time machine
for $800?
(Sheldon:)In a Venn diagram,
that would be an individual located...
(Sheldon:)...within the intersection of
"no longer want time machine"...
...and "need $800."
(Howard:)It's actually a tremendous bargain.
(Howard:)Even with shipping,
it works out to less than $4 a pound.
Cocktail shrimp are 12.50.
How are we gonna get it upstairs?
(Howard:)If we take the dish off,
it might fit in the elevator.
(Leonard:)Yes, but the elevator's been broken
for two years.
(Sheldon:)I've been meaning to ask you, do you think
we should make a call about that?
(Howard:)Not necessary.
I have a Master's in engineering.
(Howard:)I remotely repair satellites
on a regular basis.
I troubleshoot space-shuttle payloads.